<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<folder>
		<path>./Puyo Puyo 4</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo~n</name>
		<desc>Puyo Puyo~n (also called Puyo Puyo 4, based on a Japanese playword), is the fourth installment of the Puyo Puyo puzzle game series. It features a three-stage beginner mode and a single player story mode, where the main character (Arle) and (in console versions) the allies she meets along the way encounter different characters in a circus setting, and engage them in a Puyo Puyo puzzle battle.

Story Mode features different rules per level (ex. Point Puyo can drop instead of Nuisance Puyo, a certain number of colors can be used, etc.) and special attacks that can be engaged with multiple chains.
Other modes include classic Puyo Puyo and a battle mode for up to four players.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./puyo-puyo-4.gdi</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo~n</name>
		<desc>Puyo Puyo~n (also called Puyo Puyo 4, based on a Japanese playword), is the fourth installment of the Puyo Puyo puzzle game series. It features a three-stage beginner mode and a single player story mode, where the main character (Arle) and (in console versions) the allies she meets along the way encounter different characters in a circus setting, and engage them in a Puyo Puyo puzzle battle.

Story Mode features different rules per level (ex. Point Puyo can drop instead of Nuisance Puyo, a certain number of colors can be used, etc.) and special attacks that can be engaged with multiple chains.
Other modes include classic Puyo Puyo and a battle mode for up to four players.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Comp • Puzzle / Falling Block</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis (USA).cue</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis : Sega Professional Tennis</name>
		<desc>Imagine how a tennis player feels when he enters the arena, the crowd is cheering, the atmosphere electric, the adrenalin rushes... Well now you can with Virtua tennis, the most lifelike and playable tennis game ever! Play as one of eight licensed players and uncover the secret stars. As well as the traditional arcade mode you can play in the exhibition mode, with 4 player action via doubles play.

Once you've mastered those modes take on the world in the world circuit mode, with unique training games, diffrent challenges and shops to buy clothing, equipment, stages and playing partners. 
Virtua Tennis, so realistic you can almost taste the strawberries and cream.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Comp • Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240820T194232</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soulcalibur (USA).cue</path>
		<name>SoulCalibur</name>
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games.  A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends.  

All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.  In addition to high, mid, and low attacks, characters can hold/throw, block, and perform special attacks -- one or more of which is deemed "un-blockable" and must be avoided by ducking, jumping, or rotating around your attacker. 

In addition to several locales in which to fight and alternate models/costumes per character, the Dreamcast conversion of Soul Calibur contains many additional features over the arcade coin-op, including hidden characters and locales, a campaign mode, and tournament mode.  There is also a "museum" where you can view character profiles and view motion-captured martial arts demonstrations.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Comp • VS / Weapon</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240822T205716</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
